Welcome to the video on best practices for creating A+ content.
Using this tool,
you can describe your product features in a different way by including a unique
brand story, enhanced images, and text placements.
Adding A+ to your product
detail pages can result in higher conversion rates, increased traffic, and
increased sales when used effectively.
In order to add A+ content to your
listings, you would need to be a professional seller and have your brand
already enrolled in the Amazon brand registry.
Only when this is done and
your listings have been created with a correct brand name, would you be able to
add A+ content for your listings?
There are no fees associated with A+ content.
A+ content seems most appealing when it is short and succinct.
Any content that is
overlong might not inspire a buyer to read it entirely.
Create comparisons with
your other items or models.
To do this, you now have access to six additional
modules.
Comparison chart, single image and sidebar, four image highlights, single
image and specs detail, single image and highlights, and image and light text
overlay.
You can find these modules in the select new module page when you add a
module to your A+ template.
Combine images with text to create a better
experience for the buyer.
Ensure that the images are of high resolution as
images generally provide a better buyer experience.
The A+ content needs to go
through the review process with the appropriate team to ensure that it meets
guidelines.
After you've been approved, you'll be able to add A+ content only to
products that are part of your approved brand catalog.
Next, let us get content
that is restricted or prohibited.
One, mention of seller authorization such as
product only sold by authorized resellers.
Two, any warranty or guarantee
satisfaction claims or references to off Amazon return or refund references.
Three, pricing or promotion references such as affordable, cheap, bonus, free.
Language directing customers to purchase such as buy now, add to cart, get yours
now or shop with us.
Four, information about shipping details such as free
shipping or shipping timelines.
Five, use of copyright, trademark or registered
symbols anywhere in your text.
Six, boastful comments such as top-selling product,
hottest product or number one selling product.
Seven, time sensitive product
information such as on sale now, best new product of the year or references to
holidays.
Eight, adding more than two editorial or third-party quotes.
Quotes
must be from well-known publications or public figures.
Product award
information must be presented with a disclaimer.
Nine, blurry or low quality
images.
Ten, images containing watermarks or unreadable text.
Font size must be 16
or larger and readable against its background.
11, any kind of restricted
text.
This brings us to the end of this video on best practices for adding A+
content.
Thank you and happy selling on Amazon!